Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 5 (Box 1552)
    - Verso: Before the banquet at Guayaquil, Ecuador; Governor of Guayas Province sitting with Maj. Dargue, 25-verso
    - A formation of Peruvian planes that met us at Lima., 26
    - Verso: A formation of Peruvian planes that met us at Lima., 26-verso
    - A grand party as guests of Governor of Province at Arequipa, Peru., 27
    - Verso: A grand party as guests of Governor of Province at Arequipa, Peru., 27-verso
    - [photograph of certificate presented to Major. H. A. Dargue from the President of Bolivia] Verso: The diploma of the Order of the Condor of the Andes, Bolivia, 28
    - Verso: The diploma of the Order of the Condor of the Andes, Bolivia, 28-verso
    - On the rocky coast of Chile, 29
    - Verso: On the rocky coast of Chile, 29-verso
    - Services at the pier over bodies of Woolsey + Benton, B.A. [Buenos Aries], 30
    - Verso: Services at the pier over bodies of Woolsey + Benton, B.A. [Buenos Aries], 30-verso
    - Learnig the church after the funeral sermon, B/A [Buenos Aries], 31
    - Verso: Learnig the church after the funeral sermon, B/A [Buenos Aries], 31-verso
    - Taking the caskets on board at B.A [Buenos Aries], 32
    - Verso: Taking the caskets on board at B.A [Buenos Aries], 32-verso
    - Calling on the President of Uruguay, 33
    - Verso: Calling on the President of Uruguay, 33-verso
    - Montevideo, At the flying school, 34
    - Verso: Montevideo, At the flying school, 34-verso
    - Martinique, 35
    - Verso: Martinique, 35-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 6 (Box 1552)
    - Port-au-Prince, Haiti; Professor Beehe's[?] ship in background. On his studies of sub marine life, 1
    - Verso: Port-au-Prince, Haiti; Professor Beehe's[?] ship in background. On his studies of sub marine life, 1-verso
    - Bolling Field, Award of D.F.C., 2
    - Verso: Bolling Field, Award of D.F.C., 2-verso
    - Over the Carribbean en route to Colombia, 3
    - Verso: Over the Carribbean en route to Colombia, 3-verso
    - ["Detroit", "San Francisco", "St. Louis" passing Porto Bello, R.P. en route to Bogota, Columbia. Pan-American Flight.], 4
    - Over the Carribbean, 5
    - Verso: Over the Carribbean, 5-verso
    - Caption: "Pan American Flight" Off Porto Bello R.P. en route France Field to Columbia[Colombia], 6
    - Caption: Off Pueeblo Neuvo going south from Panama City, R.P. "Pan American Flight"; Verso: Note the 5 planes + their shadows - Off on the long stretch down the west coast of S.A., 7
    - Verso: Note the 5 planes + their shadows - Off on the long stretch down the west coast of S.A., 7-verso
    - Caption: The "New York" over Gatun Lake, C.Z. "Pan American Flight", 8
    - The San Francisco nearly on the rocks at Montevideo, 9
    - Verso: The San Francisco nearly on the rocks at Montevideo, 9-verso
    - The accident at B.A. [Buenos Aries], 10
    - Verso: The accident at B.A. [Buenos Aries], 10-verso
    - Reception + dance at Military school; Caracas Venez., 11
    - Verso: Reception + dance at Military school; Caracas Venez., 11-verso
    - Puerto Cabello, Venez., 12
    - Verso: Puerto Cabello, Venez., 12-verso
    - Puerto Cabello, Venezuela, 13
    - Verso: Puerto Cabello, Venezuela, 13-verso
    - The harbor at Rio with Naval Air Station + flying field in foreground, 14
    - Verso: The harbor at Rio with Naval Air Station + flying field in foreground, 14-verso
    - Port-au-Prince, Haiti, 15
    - Verso: Port-au-Prince, Haiti, 15-verso
    - A little lunch at Port-au-Price. Incidentally weather (not lunch) hot at Hades! [?], 16
    - Verso: A little lunch at Port-au-Price. Incidentally weather (not lunch) hot at Hades! [?], 16-verso
    - Getting a banquet from the Mayor of Port-au-prince upon our arrival., 17
    - Verso: Getting a banquet from the Mayor of Port-au-prince upon our arrival., 17-verso
    - At Port-au-Prince; The Mayor (left) had just presented the banquet., 18
    - Verso: At Port-au-Prince; The Mayor (left) had just presented the banquet., 18-verso
    - Refueling at Port of Spain, 19
    - Verso: Refueling at Port of Spain, 19-verso
    - Maintenance work at Cayenne, 20
    - Verso: Maintenance work at Cayenne, 20-verso
    - Minister Cook and P.A.F. at Caracas, 21
    - Verso: Minister Cook and P.A.F. at Caracas, 21-verso
    - Enterance to exposition grounds showing[?] resturant, Lima., 22
    - Verso: Enterance to exposition grounds showing[?] resturant, Lima., 22-verso
    - Suburbs of Guayaquil, 23
    - Verso: Suburbs of Guayaquil, 23-verso
    - Public library, Guayaquil, 24
    - Verso: Public library, Guayaquil, 24-verso
    - Private library - Guayaquil, 25
    - Verso: Private library - Guayaquil, 25-verso
    - Astronomical Observatory Quito, Ecuador; One of the highest in the world, 26
    - Verso: Astronomical Observatory Quito, Ecuador; One of the highest in the world, 26-verso
    - Country near Guayaquil, 27
    - Verso: Country near Guayaquil, 27-verso
    - In the country near Guayaquil, Ecuador, 28
    - Verso: In the country near Guayaquil, Ecuador, 28-verso
    - Roof of the Capilla Seal - Cholulu [Puebla] Mexico, 29
    - Verso: Roof of the Capilla Seal - Cholulu [Puebla] Mexico, 29-verso
    - House formerly occupied by Alvarado Cortez, Mexico, 30
    - Verso: House formerly occupied by Alvarado Cortez, Mexico, 30-verso
    - Public gardens in Quito, 31
    - Verso: Public gardens in Quito, 31-verso
    - Theobroma[?] cocoa, 32
    - Verso: Theobroma[?] cocoa, 32-verso
    - Pases[?] of de la Reforma - City of Mexico, 33
    - Verso: Pases[?] of de la Reforma - City of Mexico, 33-verso
    - Caudron Hydroplane, 34
    - Verso: Caudron Hydroplane, 34-verso
    - [Crane lifting a Pan-American Flight plane out of the water], 35
    - LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane that will be used on the Pan American Flight shown here as a sea plane., 36
    - Verso: LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane that will be used on the Pan American Flight shown here as a sea plane., 36-verso
    - [The wheel of a Pan-American plane], 37
    - LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane to be used on the Pan-American Flight, 38
    - Verso: LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane to be used on the Pan-American Flight, 38-verso
    - LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane that will be used on the Pan American Flight shown landing in water, 39
    - Verso: LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane that will be used on the Pan American Flight shown landing in water, 39-verso
    - The plane to be used on P.A.F., 40
    - Verso: The plane to be used on P.A.F., 40-verso
    - Taking off, 41
    - Verso: Taking off, 41-verso
    - Long Island Sound, 42
    - Verso: Long Island Sound, 42-verso
    - Caption: San Antonio damaged at France Field, 43
  Box 1553 - Box 1556
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1557 - Box 1560
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  Box 1561 - Box 1565
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6